<resources>
    <string name="app_name">COVID-19 SL</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open Navigation Panel</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close Navigation Panel</string>

    <string name="dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="symptoms_description">
        The Coronavirus pandemic has erupted in Sri Lanka and here are the symptoms one should look
        out for if they suspect they have contacted the disease.\n\n
        1. Cough\n
        2. Fever\n
        3. Shortness of Breath\n
        4. Headache\n
        5. Runny Nose\n
        6. Sore Throat\n
        \nHaving these symptoms doesn’t mean you have COVID-19.
        However, since these are common symptoms of the COVID-19 infection,
        for the sake of those close to you, please follow the measures mentioned below.
        Understand that this is part of your national responsibility.\n
        \nDo not leave home for any reason other than seeking medical advice.\n
        \nIf possible, use a separate room for yourself.\n
        \nAlways keep a distance of at least one meter between yourself and others at home.\n
        \nIf possible, use a separate washroom. If this is not possible, always wash the taps, doorknobs etc. after use with soap and water.\n
        \nDo not encourage visitors to the house.\n
        \nFrequently wash your hands for at least 20 seconds with soap and water. Ask your family members to do the same.\n
        \nUse separate cups, plates, towels, bedspreads etc. Wash them separately with soap and water.\n
        \nCover your mouth and nose with a disposable tissue or the inside of your elbow when coughing and sneezing. Safely dispose of the used tissues.\n
        \nDo not reuse face masks and gloves etc. Dispose them in a garbage bin with a lid.\n
        \nIf you have returned from abroad or associated someone who has COVID-19 or someone suspected of being infected within the past 14 days, immediately report to the Public Health Inspector (PHI) or the Medical Officer of Health (MOH) of your area.\n
        \nCall 1999 hotline for medical and other advice regarding Covid-19.\n
        \nCall 1990 for ambulance facilities in case of an emergency.
    </string>
    <string name="workplace_prevention_description">
        We spend more time at work places. So we need to care more about how to protect places that
        work against COVID-19. Follow these instructions to keep your work safe.\n
        \nIf anyone shows light symptoms such as fever, cough or cold, advise him not to go to work
        until it is fully healed. If possible, encourage me to work from home.\n
        \nClean the equipment used by more than one person like door handles, phone receivers,
        table surface, stapler.\n
        \nWash your hands well often using soap. Avoid touching your face, mouth, nose and eyes.
        COVID-19 virus is usually spread through contact.\n
        \nAvoid increasing the crowd as much as possible. Snooze meetings and follow modern
        communication methods such as video conferencing and group calling.\n
        \nIf you reduce the chance to spread the corona virus at your workplace, you may also reduce
        the chance of immune to your beloved family members.\n
    </string>

</resources>
